[{"answer": "Well, yes it is.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "This is a pretty big scandal, isn't it, Douglas Brinkley?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "It's not going to make -- no, it's not going to make a whole lot of difference.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Should it make much difference?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Well, we have to keep the word \"allegations\" out there right now.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Is it that serious?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Meredith, how are you?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "No, I'm serious.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "Why is it?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "Yes, we should.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Shall we move off this rather uncomfortable subject?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Because I reckon you'd have a pretty good view of this.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "I think probably raising your children is the hardest thing you can do and the most rewarding, obviously, because you are -- you are shaping lives, you know.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Which is harder?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Yes, you know, I'm going to stick up a little bit for Hilary here.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "What did you make of the row with Ann Romney, then, because it did seem a very strange battleground for any senior Democrats to pick?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "I -- I'm surprised she's not drunk every day.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "When you see something like that, what -- what do you make of it?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Yes, I do, Piers.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "Do you think America is ready for its first female president?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "I'm leaving.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "I want to talk to you about what you think of \"The Today Show\" losing its crown against \"GMA\" without you, obviously?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "It wasn't a miniskirt.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "What's going on?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "I was heading toward the bathroom.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Where were you, Meredith, when you first heard of the Lauer deal?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Reunite the -- the dream team?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Well, I hope that Ann has enough perspective, and I'm sure that she does, to ignore it.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "What -- what do you think of that?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Yes, I don't know.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "-- somebody like Sarah Palin, a rather divisive politician, to be, effectively, a \"Today Show\" host?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "So we should take this seriously, presumably?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Well, Angelo Guglielmo, who is the producer, he brought us sort of a demo reel or, for lack of a better term, to show us what he was working on.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "When you saw this story, what gave you the desire to make a -- a film about it?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "I mean it was a real -- it's a (INAUDIBLE) of a -- a weird thriller, isn't it?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "It does in the sense that, yes, she was a comfort but it was also a terrible betrayal.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "Because, in the end, if she was a comfort to them, how much does it really matter that she actually invented her own story?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "I plan to take over the -- in fact, your show is the next thing I plan to control.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "I mean, there's no stopping you, is there?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Well during the breast feeding stage, Greg, infants can get very confused and upset when they're separated from their mothers.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "What are you doing there?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "No, my heart swells with pride.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Now, Robert, when I -- when you see a trailer like that -- and we have dozens of great movies to choose from, and we choose the one of you wearing mammary glands in \"Meet the Fockers,\" does your heart swell with pride or does part of you think why the hell couldn't you have done something, you know, a little bit more serious for the great man?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Well, we -- I was in Midtown when we were -- when it happened.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "What went through your mind and how quickly did you think I've got to do something like this?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Well, it -- it happened with a lot of help from a lot of amazing people, as you said, Nelson Mandela and Martin Scorsese and Barry Levinson and Hugh Grant and studios such as Universal Pictures and Warner Brothers and just volunteers and amazing New Yorkers.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "But how did you turn that into what has become not just a -- a New York event, but a -- an international event and one that now generates really big money for New York?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "I mean it's been -- it's been, as I say, remarkably successful.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "And how could we do something -- what was our creative response to our community and what could we do to just help and give people a new memory to want to come back downtown?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Well, I -- downtown has recovered in a lot of ways.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "But, Robert, what do you think about America's recovery from 9/11 generally?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "No, go ahead.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Well, it -- you want to?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "the middle class is suffering, as we all know.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "And, Robert, what would you say?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "E NIRO: Well, I think it's still that.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "How do you get America's image, if you like, its reputation, back as the great land of opportunity?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "I absolutely do, yes.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Do you -- do you agree with -- do you agree with President Obama's campaign, this Warren Buffet Rule, that the weal -- the very wealthiest Americans should pay a lot more tax?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "Well, I'll do whatever I have to do, whatever's fair.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Would you object to -- would you object to paying more?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Low, yes, very low.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Astoundingly low?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Oh, God, that's another big question.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "What do you think of that law in modern America?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "E NIRO: Well, Leonardo DiCaprio is a -- a very serious young actor.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "One is, who, to you, is the greatest actor living today, male or female?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "Oh, it's great being a -- a parent and -- and my kids are -- I have older kids and younger kids, obviously.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "How -- how is -- how is fatherhood six time around going?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "I like the idea of the festival not only being just a festival, it's a -- it's a cultural thing.", "docId": "120416pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "What do you hope it says about your city, New York?", "qSentId": 667}]